Madison Wells

7307 Creekwood Quorum Dr Apt 102 Charlotte, NC, 28212 jwells.me@gmail.com 704-651-0911

Computer science professional and enthusiast with several years of experience in the IT/CS field. Works well with others, as well as individually. Strong problem-solving skills and ability to learn quickly. Passionate about computers and helping others.

Looking for work in software development.

Professional Experience

Network/Security Technician IT/OT Cybersecurity

Duke Energy Corporation, Charlotte, North Carolina, United States | December 2020 -Present

Office Assistant

Food Lion, Denver, North Carolina, United States | April 2020 - October 2020

Technical Operations Intern

TKXS, Raleigh, North Carolina, United States | October 2019 - January 2020

IT Walk-in Technician

ITS UNC, Chapel Hill, North Carolina, United States | January 2019 - August 2019

Front End Supervisor

Food Lion, Denver, North Carolina, United States | February 2018 - August 2018

Residential Computing Consultant

ResNET University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill, Chapel Hill, North Carolina, United States | August 2017 - December 2017

Data Transfer Clerk

First Residential Services, Charlotte, North Carolina, United States | May 2017 - July 2017

- Interfaces with Telecom, Firewall, and Silent Defense/Splunk engineer teams, providing high-level technical support on a variety of network hardware (Palo Alto, Cisco, Ixia, Dell, OpenGear).
- Handles NERC CIP secure information and IP addresses.
- Oversees production process from inventory through final shipment.
- Troubleshooting configurations on Cisco switches and routers.
- Managed customer service, dealing with a large variety of customers.
- Handled accounting work with large values of currency, sorting and organizing.
- Supervised and managed the front-end and the employees there.
- Provided technical support, software installation, configuration, and troubleshooting around the office.
- Reorganized hardware and fixed old computers (desktops, laptops, etc.).
- Performed bash script programming involving Heroku and AWS integration.
- Worked at walk-in IT service desk at UNC Chapel Hill providing customer service and troubleshooting clients' computers.
- Performed malware removal/cleanup.
- General software maintenance (removing slow software, providing updates, etc.).
- · Assisted with hardware troubleshooting.
- Provided software installation.
- Managed customer service, dealing with a large variety of customers
- Handled accounting work with large values of currency, sorting and organizing
- Supervised and managed front-end and the employees there
- Provided tech support for UNC's residents, doing service calls to dorms.
- Assisted residents with malware removal, set-up of new devices, connecting devices to the University's WiFi, and more.
- Hosted events involving ResNET-owned equipment and technology.
- Performed back-end data processing on large quantities of data.
- Maintained client privacy when handling sensitive data.
- Minor VI BASIC programming in Excel for management of massive spreadsheets.

Education

Studied BS in Computer Science

University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill | August 2016 - May 2019

High School Diploma

North Carolina School of Science and Mathematics | August 2014 - June 2016

Key Skills

- Attention to detail
- Problem-solving
- Organization
- Software development
- JavaScript
- HTML/CSS
- Python

- Java
- (
- Teamwork
- Technical documentation
- Time management
- Flexibility
- Work independently